Guide to the John McCarthy Papers SC0524
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2012-055
  - Non-Monotone Reasoning files
    - Non-Mono Dups M-S (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Non-Mono M-S (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Non-Mono T-Z (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Non-Monotonic Reasoning (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Nonmonotonic Library (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Non-Mono A-F (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Non-Mono G-L (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Alpha Files
    - Albus, James S. (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Abbott, Russell J. (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Aczel, Peter (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Ajenstat, Henri (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Allen, F. E. (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Allen, John (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Ambler, Allen L. (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Andrews, Peter (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Anisimov (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Antoni, Giovanni D. (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Ashcroft, E. A. (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Aspvall, Bengt (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - AAAI (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - AAAI Workshops (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - ABL (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - ACM (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Access to Energy (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - AI Project Admin (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Abstract Syntax and Semantics of Programs To Go (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Academic Council (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Advice Taken (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Algebraic Simplification (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Air Sickness Bags (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Airline (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Alaska (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Algebraic Language (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - ALGOL (1 of 2) (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - ALGOL (2 of 2) (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Ambiguity Tolerance (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Appointments (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - April 1979 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous 1977-1979 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Arnold, R. David (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Colby (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Crocker (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Tesler, L.G. (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Wagner, Todd (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Weiner, Peter (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Elschlager, R. (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Ginsparg, Jerrold (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Harvey, Brian (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Levy, David (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Sintzoff, Michel (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Stark, W. Richard (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Swinehart, Dan (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - ARPA (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Assignments (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Automated Biological Lab with Glazer, Minsky (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Ascribing (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Baker, T.P. (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - De Bakker, J.W. (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Barringer, H. (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Barzden, J.M. (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Baskett, Forest (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Bauer, F.L. (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Bibel, Wolfgang (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Bledsoe, W.W. (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Bobrow, Daniel G. (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Bochmann, Gregor (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Bosack, L. (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Bourbaki, Nicholas (Peter?) (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Bayer (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Brooks (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Buchanan (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Bukovsky (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Bulnes (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Burstall (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Buvac, Sasa (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Bad Ideas (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - Barwise (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - Bibliography (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Biography (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Book (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Brattle Research re: MAD Intelligent Systems (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Britannica (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Budget (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Cartwright (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Cheeseman, Peter (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Budget (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Chin, David Ngi (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Chou, Shang-Chin (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Chudnovsky, David (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Clancy, William J. (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Codfish, Michael (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Costello, Tom (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - The Future of Cars, Energy, Environment, Economics. January 27-28 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - CASBS (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - CBCL (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Center for Democracy in the USSR (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Centre Mondial 1985- (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Chernobyl (1 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Chernobyl (2 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Chess (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Chowning (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Circle Generator (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Circuit Layout (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Circumscription (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Class (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - CS323 Nonmonotonic Reasoning (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - CS323 1993 Handout #1 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - STS160 1998 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Clean Air (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Clippings (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - COBOL (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - For Commitments (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Common Sense Slides (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Compiler (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Comprehensive (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Computer Center (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Computer Control Lab (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Computer Man Society Proceedings, Haifa (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Computer Man Society Proceedings, Haifa '79 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Computer Science Division (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Computers (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Computing Reviews (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Consciousness (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Consulting (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Creary (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - CS206 1980 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - CS258 W75 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - CSD (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - CSD-CF (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - CVLIK (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Current Teaching (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Davis, Byron (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Davis, Ernest (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Deck Setup for a Lisp Job (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Dennis, Jack B. (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Deransart, Pierre (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Dincbas, M. (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Doyle (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Drabent, Wlodzimierz (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Dreyfus, H. (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Drummond, Mark E. (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Dialog (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Dialog systems (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Dues and Subs (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - DuPont Article from FORTUNE (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Edelman, Shimon (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Ershov, Andrei (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - EBOS including IBM RT (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Educational Literature (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Educational Remarks (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - EKL (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Elementary Programming (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - Elephant (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - Elephant Lecture (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Electrochemical Lab (Tokyo) (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Energy (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Environmental Material (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Expense (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Fagin (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Falkenhaimer, Brian (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Feferman, Solomon (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Feigenbaum, E.A. (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Fiat, Amos (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Freiling, Chris (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Friedlander (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Futamura, Yoshihiko (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Feldman (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Filman (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Finlayson (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Fredkin (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Fall Joint Programming Race (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - The Feasibility of Interstellar Travel (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - From brown notebook OAI (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Forsythe (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Future of scientific publication slides (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Gabriel, Richard P. (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Ganapathy (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Gardner, A. (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Gazdar, Gerald (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Gelfund, I.M. (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Genesereth (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Gennery, Donald B. (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Georgeff, Michael P. (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Gerson, Elihu M. (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Ginsberg, M. (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Ginsberg, Matthew (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Goad, C. (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Goguen, Joseph A. (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Golden, Donald (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Gordon, M. (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Gorin (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Gosling, James (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Jasper, R. (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Granlund, Goesta H. (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Green (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Greenberg, Nina (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Greenblatt (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Gries, D. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Griss, M. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Grosof, Benjamin (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Grosz, Barbara (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Glasnost (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Government Support (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Graduate Students (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Grants and Reviews (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Hagert, Goran (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Haneclou, Peter (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Hanks, Steve (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Hannah (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Hanson, Robin (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Haugland (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Hayes-Roth, Barbara (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Hayes (1 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Hayes (2 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Hedlund, Martin (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Hewitt, Carl (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Hilts, P. (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Hillis, Daniel W. (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Hin Tikka (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Hirsch, M. (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Hobbs, Jerry (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Hobbs (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Hoffman, William C. (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Hofstadter, Douglas (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Holloway, David (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Hooman, Jozef (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Hopcroft, John (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Houri, A. (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Huberman, Bernardo (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - Hung (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Hunt, Warren A., Jr. (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Hunter, Maxwell W. II (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - Hurlbert, Anya (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - Hyde, Roderick A. (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - Howard (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - Hieronymus (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - High Frontier (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - HIJCAI Politics (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Home Terminal Paper (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - IBM (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Ideas for Project (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - IFIP Congress '65 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - IFIP Papers (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Incomplete Work (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - India (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Inference (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Possible Forms of Intelligence (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - J (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - K (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Kiessling, Werner (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Knutsson, H. (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Komorowski, H.J. (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Konolige, Kurt (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Korf, Richard E. (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Kowalski, Robert (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Knowledge (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Knowledge 1986 Man (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Knowledgebase (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Jean-Louis Lassez (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Lloyd, J.W. (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - L (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Lighthill Review Master (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Lighthill Review Copies (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Levinthal (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Licklider (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Lederberg (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Letters (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Letters - low priority (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Workshop on Planning and Reasoning about Action, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Library Listings (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - LISP Functions (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - LMC (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - LISP Book (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Little Thoughts (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Martin (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - McDermott, Drew (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - M (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - McMahon Squares Puzzles, Etc. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Menzel (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Minsky (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Moore, Robert C. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Moravec, Hans P. (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - MAD (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - MAIL to Answer (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Manuscripts (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Math Sci (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - MCC (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Misc (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Misc Reprints (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - MTC (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Missionaries & Cannibals (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - My Notes (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Names (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - National Association of Scholars (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Notes Sept-Oct 79 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Naivete (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Names & Numbers (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Nat. Res. Council (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - New Computer (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Not In Our Genes (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Notes (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Non-Monotonic Slides (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Notebooks (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Notes (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Notes June 74 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - JMC Notes (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Research Notes, TS (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Research Notes, AI (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Natl Academy of Sciences (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - National Academy of Sciences 2 (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - NCD (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Natl. Assoc. Sch. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - 1987 August - November (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Notes (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Notebooks (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Notes 3 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Notes 4 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Notes 5 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Notes 6 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Obstacle (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - N (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Nilsson, Martin (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Old Corresp. JMC (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - P-Q (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Parallel Computing (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Passport & Visas (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Philosophy Papers (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - PYLYSHYN (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Papers Being Revised (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - PROLOG (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - PDP 1 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - PDP (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - 7090 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Proposals (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Projects (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Personnel (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Prospective Visitors (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Provin (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Philosophy and AI (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Philosophy Reprints (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Project Ind. (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Propaganda (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Parallel Computer (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Petition (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - P (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Perlis, Donald (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Perry, John (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Petrie, Charles, Jr. (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Phelps, John B. (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Popplestone, Robin (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Przymusinski, Teodor C. (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Queens (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Q. 32 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - R (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Reiter, Raymond (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Restivo (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Ringle (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Real Time Language (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Recursion Article (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Refile (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Report Lists (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Refereeing and Reviewing (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Requests (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Revolution (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - S (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Science and Society (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Scientific American Article (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Scientific American (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Soviet Bureaucracies Souvenirs (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - SDI (Box 41, Folder 39)
    - Soviet Computing (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - SDI (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - STO (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Spring 1979 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Sigma Xi Lecture (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Searle Slides (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Senate (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Stanford Senate (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - IJCAI Trip (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Sh-Sz (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Shapiro, Ehud (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Shoham, Yoav (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Spee, Paul (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Simple Simon (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Slides - Use of Computer in Offices (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Sloman (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Study Groub [sic] Business (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Sustainability (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Samizdat bulletin (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Sa-Sg (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Safra, Shmuel (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Sandewall, Erik (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Sergot, M. J. (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Slides and transparencies (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - McCarthy Papers (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - assorted transparencies (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Unlabeled Misc. (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Space Travel (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Talcott Thesis (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Time Sharing Debugging for a Small Computer (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Int'l Symp on AI 11/13-15 - Cancun (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Symp - Bledsoe - Texas 11/15-16 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Newcastle-on-Tyne 9//7-11/92 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Transparencies (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Knowledge Slides (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Transparencies 2 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Some Expert Systems (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Terminal, Etc. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - US-Japan AI Conference (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Time Sharing Grant (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - T (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Taylor, Stephen (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Toledo, Sue (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - TWX (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - B 5000 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - U Texas (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - U-V (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - van der Poel, W. L. (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - VTSS (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - W 1 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - W 2 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Winograd, Terry (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - X-Z (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Notebooks
    - Math Theory of Computation Jan 1965 - (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - J. McCarthy, Computation Center, Stanford, Calif.94305 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - 1970 B (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - 1970 C (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Fall 1970 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - 1970? A (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Dec 1970 D (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Dec. 1970 E (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Computers in Number Theory/Number Theory/Elementary Number Theory/Cours d'Arithmatique (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - 1972 July (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Dec 1973 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Dec 1974 A (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Dec 1974 B (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - May 1977 I. Knowledge (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - 9 June 1977 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - 1977 Sept 18 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Dec 19, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - 1982 A (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Round the world in '78 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - July 8, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - circa 1980? (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - circa 1975 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - 1981 Sept 15 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - June 19, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - 1981 June 11. Contains draft of Coloring Maps and the Kowalski Doctrine (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - 1981 May 26. ANL (artificial natural language) (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - 1982 April 17 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - 1982 Aug 19 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - 1982 April 22 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - 1982 April 19, 1982 July 1. Contents: p. 7 - Theory of dirty LISP; p 15 - locally dirty append. (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - 1982 Aug 11 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - 1982 Sept 4 (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - 1983 June 27 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - 1983 Sept 13 (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - from 1983 Dec 19 to 1984 Jun 21 (Box 44, Folder 35)
    - 1984 June 20 - 1984 Sept 10 (Box 44, Folder 36)
    - 1984 Dec 20 - 1985 Mar 26 (Box 44, Folder 37)
    - 1985 June 12 - 1985 Sept 19 (Box 44, Folder 38)
    - 1985 Sept 19 - 1986 Mar 21 (Box 44, Folder 39)
    - 1986 Mar 22 - 1986 Aug 14 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - 1986 Aug 14 - 1986 Dec 4 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - 1986 Dec 4 - 1987 May 6 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - 1987 May 6 - 1987 July 11 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - 1987 July 12 - 1987 Oct 5 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - 1987 Oct 14 - (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - 1988 Mar 1 - 1988 June 20 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - 1988 June 21 - 1988 Nov 14 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - 1988 Nov 14 - 1989 April 25 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - 1989 Apr 26 - 1989 Dec 31 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - 1990 June 1 - July 15 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - 1990 July 29 - (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - 1990 Sept 16 - November (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - 3.15 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - 1991 Jan 27 - 1991 Nov 13 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - 1992 May 1 - 1992 Nov 20 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - 1993 June 20 - (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - 97 Nov 7 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - 2000 May 31 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - small red Memo book (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - small green Mead Memo book (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - small spiral-bound green checked notebook (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - 41176 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - small green checked notebook (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - small hot pink notebook (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - small yellow notebook (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - 1988 Aug 3 (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - blue spiral-bound notebook (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Misc
    - Formal Reas. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Port. Comm. Lisp. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - DARPA Hardware (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Basic AI (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - EBOS (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Theorem Prov. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Advanced R & D (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - QLISP (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - DARPA Contract Information (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Technology Essay (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Elephant (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - JMC notes, handwritten (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Slides (1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Slides (2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - 2004 Aug B (1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - 2004 Aug B (2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - 2004 Aug C (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - 2004 Sept B (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - CSLI Monthly (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Conference Record of the 1980 LISP Conference (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - QLISP (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - LISP Programming and Proving (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Elephant (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Umbrella Feb 89 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Loose Misc. (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Outgoing Correspondence (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - 1989 Correspondence - JMC (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - JMC 1989-1990 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - LISP History 1 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - References for JMC LISP (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - LISP History 2 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Commonsense (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Rec. Humor (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Solutions for CS 257A's Final (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - CS226 Wtr. 1981. Epistem. Problems of AI (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - PROLOG 1982 CS321 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - CS204 1982 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - CS206 Fall 1982 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - CS226 Winter 82-83 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - CS206 1983 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - CS258 W84 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - CS157A Winter 84 Reading Course (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - CS157 Winter 1983 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - CS157B Spring 1983 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - CS323 Reader (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - CS258 notes (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - CS 221 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - CS 323 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - CS306 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - CS 221 1990 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - CS157 1991 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - CS242 F92 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - CS 323 Winter 90 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - CS 323 1992 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - CS 157 1992 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Common Sense '93 Working Papers (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Non-Monotonic Reasoning Workshop (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - CS 323 Winter 1996 Reader (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Stanford Artificial Intelligence Project (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Final Report: Research in Mathematical Theory of Computation (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - LISP Programming and Proving (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Library (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Papers (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Papers (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - NSF MCS81-11586 2 FCZ 432 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - 2FCZ 451 163C 187 NSF MCS 82-06565 JMC-Ketonen (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - AFOSR 2FCZ464 AFOSR81-0014 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - 2 FCZ762 ARPA N00039-82-C-0250 McCarthy (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - ARPA Equipment 2FCZ780 MDA903 83 C0188 187X007 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - 2FCZ913 IBM 192T412 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - JMC Japan NSF (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - 2M-AFOSR 84-85 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Gabriel Proposal (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Portable Common LISP ARPA Proposal (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - JMC NSF Renewal (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - 2M/Pnueli NSF (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - JMC/Goad MCS-8305026 NSF 1983-85 (Box 48, Folder 23)